So if I were to create a frozen yogurt store,
this is how I would do it.
So when I was 21, I was deciding between this,
test prep, and fitness.
So number one, I would open my own frozen yogurt store,
and so here are the numbers on the top
five frozen yogurt franchises in the US.
Owner pay, as you can see, after everything, super slim.
Number two, store setup.
So most frozen yogurt store owners
charge 25 cents to 60 cents per ounce,
and yogurt costs about eight cents per ounce,
and that's pretty high margin.
Toppings cost, on the other hand,
10 to 40 cents per ounce, which is typically low margin.
Since the average cup size is eight ounces,
I would line the store up from highest to lowest margin.
And so you grab your cup, you choose your yogurt,
then you choose your hard toppings,
then you choose your fresh toppings.
So number three, cup size.
I would only serve medium and large cups,
because when you give someone a bigger cup,
they're more likely to fill it.
If you have a bucket like this,
and then you have to eat frozen yogurt out of it,
and the bucket's this big, you're like,
well, shoot, I gotta kind of fill it up a little bit,
otherwise it looks dumb.
Number four, self-serve.
So most business owners charge for small, medium, large,
but what actually is super smart in this industry specifically
is they charge by weight,
which the consumer is in control of.
Number five, I would try and become
the Chick-fil-A of the industry.
So Yogurtland, Menchies, Goldenspoon,
they're all almost exactly the same.
There is no Chick-fil-A in the business,
which you can do with these three things.
And so number six, marketing.
So I would set up close to colleges
and partner with fraternities and sororities
and have competitions between them
to see who could get the most yogurt
and give them some sort of merch
or the most yogurt during that period of time.
And I'd also have crazy, like, 50% off types incentives
to get customer numbers in, so I could acquire a lead
that I could get lifetime value on for a couple bucks.
These are just some of the tiny taxes
that actually move the needle in businesses.
If you wanna learn how to take your business
to the next level and beyond,
from someone who owns a $250 million annual portfolio,
you can comment map for personalized roadmap
showing you exactly how we do it.